This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Makini Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum-gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Luffy was sent flying from the Sabaody Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma.
After soaring through the sky for hours,
he found himself in a kingdom inhabited entirely by women.
Its name was Amazon Lily.
Everyone falls in love!
Pirate Empress Hancock!
Sorry I can't pay you back for saving my life and stuff,
but I got places to go and a crew that's waiting for me!
And that means bye-bye, Lady Land!
Men truly are mysterious.
Their arms stretch, they grow fat without warning,
their chests are flat, and between their legs they have...
Ugh!
I hate to ask you for your help again, but could you take these off for me?
Your family jewels?
Would you drop it?
I mean these things!
I said I was going to see my friends, remember?
If I show up looking like this, they're all gonna laugh at me!
I think they look nice, but I suppose...
There.
Hey, thanks, Lady!
You're the best!
I can't imagine anyone hating frills.
You men are just too strange.
Yeah, well, whatever you say.
Either way, thanks for taking them off.
Okay, bye for real this time.
I gotta hurry.
Are all men so hasty?
I can't rest till I know my friends survive like I did.
That's all that matters.
Because as long as they're alive,
we can get back up and keep fighting!
I'm gonna get stronger than all those guys!
Let's do this!
I'll walk all the way back to Sabaody on my hands!
That'll toughen me up for sure!
Think you could give me a ship?
Wow, you really are hasty.
Do you have any ships?
We're in a Calm Belt?
That's right.
This island lies in an area known as a Calm Belt,
and it's surrounded by a giant den of sea canes.
That's another reason sailors never dare to come near this place.
Castaways do sometimes make their way to our shores,
but they almost always do so as corpses.
Wait, but you said your leader was part of a pirate crew, right?
The ship of our snake princess, the Yuta,
is pulled by two giant poisonous sea snakes,
so even sea kings don't dare to attack it.
And it's the only ship on Amazon Lily.
This sucks!
And there's no wind?
Should I just build a raft and paddle all the way there?
That's a joke, right?
Hey!
I'll just build a raft and paddle all the way there!
Wait, you weren't joking?
Yeah!
It died!
But it's already falling apart!
What's wrong?
He said he was a pirate, but he can't even swim?
I had no obligation to save you.
Do all men sink like a rock even if they're sailors?
That was close.
Damn it!
If only Frankie was here!
I'm screwed!
You're not the only one with problems!
Why did you have to cling to me
when you should have been running away from here?
If this keeps up much longer,
I'll end up growing attached to you!
Hold on!
Just stop!
Why do you want to shoot me?
You know, come to think of it,
these arrows are crazy strong!
When those girls were chasing me earlier,
they were busting up stone walls with those things!
Doesn't look like there's anything special about them, though!
Well, of course these arrows are strong.
They're imbued with our hockey.
You're mocking me, aren't you?
Hockey?
I never heard of it.
There she is!
Margaret, are you safe?
You made it!
The man's with her!
Strike him down!
Coward!
Come back!
Forgive me if you were injured, Margaret,
but our situation is quite dire.
The Snake Princess has returned,
so we must vanquish this fiend post-haste!
Huh?
You're quite bold to lay your anchor
in Sea King-infested waters,
unless you're just fools.
Yes, we did notice the Sea Kings, thank you.
The Sea Prism Stone on this battleship
may conceal our presence from the beasts for a while,
but after waiting here for so long,
they eventually caught on and attacked us.
We would prefer to avoid such encounters,
but as you know,
the agreement between the Kuja and the government
forbids us from getting closer
than three kilometers from your island.
So, like fools,
here we are waiting in a monster's nest
while you ladies take your sweet time.
Hey, have you heard?
They say that the ruler of the Kuja
is a monster that can turn people to stone.
That's stupid.
You killed that Sea King?
Well, you can color me impressed.
Those of us who travel on the Grand Line
are no strangers to these creatures,
but the ones here in the Calm Belt
are certainly larger and decidedly more ferocious.
Any sign of the Kuja's ship?
Uh, no, not yet, Vice Admiral.
No approaching ships anywhere in sight.
How long does she intend to keep us waiting?
Or perhaps the Empress has changed her mind?
It's a Sea King!
Fire!
No way!
Our cannons didn't even leave a mark on that thing!
The whole ship's gonna be smashed to pieces
if we don't do something quick!
Yeah, but what can we do?
We gave it all we had!
That thing isn't gonna eat the whole ship, is it?
I had hope for a greeting from the Empress,
not this monster!
However, I shall meet it all the same!
Look, guys!
He's alive!
Monster though it may be,
if I allowed that beast to devour a marine vessel!
How could I call myself a Vice Admiral?
What strange marks?
Did you cut from the inside of its stomach?
I am not here to hunt Sea Kings or to chat about them.
Let us conduct our business quickly
so that I may leave these waters.
Your words are as sharp as your blade.
Then hear them well, Kuja Pirates!
I tire of waiting here.
I am Vice Admiral Momonga of Navy Headquarters,
Warlord of the Sea,
and Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
I have come for you!
Reveal yourself!
The Snake Princess does not cater to your beck and call.
There's your answer.
You might as well go home now.
Look at those ugly men!
Unsophisticated force!
I haven't seen a live one in a long time!
Whenever pirates or merchants see the Kuja flag flying above the island,
they play in terror!
That laugh isn't very ladylike.
We received a message from your princess.
She claimed that she would reply to our summons,
but now it appears she was not quite sincere.
This morning's paper,
a place and date has been decided
for the public execution of Portgus D. Ace,
the Second Division Commander of the Whitebeard Pirates.
There is no turning back now.
The world government has issued strict orders
that the seven warlords of the sea assemble,
refuse, and our agreement will become void,
and your princess's title as warlord will be revoked.
Think about that for a moment.
Until now, you have done as you please
just because of your position.
But if you are unwilling to grant us this favor,
you will be reduced to nothing but ordinary pirates,
which means you'll be adversaries
of the Marines and world government alike.
Do you hear me?
Boa Hancock!
Boa time!
Which one of you had the audacity to place this kitten in my path?
My deepest apologies, Empress. I accept full responsibility.
You should be more careful.
Yes, of course. Stop it.
At long last, Bower Hancock.
Careful, men. Keep your guard up.
The Vice Admiral is right. I'm still not convinced those women aren't really monsters in disguise.
There's no telling how frightening their leader could be. Brace yourselves!
That's the pirate empress?
She's the most beautiful woman in the world.
Crap! Crap! Crap!
Halt, man! Face me!
Oh, jeez. The girls from this island are scary as heck.
I'll take Nami over them any day.
Well, maybe not.
That's what those crazy arrows that I've done for!
There!
Crap! Crap!
All right, here goes!
Here goes!
This fiend behaves more like a monkey than a human man.
Dammit, what are we going to do?
We cannot allow him to run free here,
not with the Empress coming.
We have no choice but to hunt him down
and kill him as quickly as possible.
Our time is short, we must split up.
Very well, may your arrows find their target, my sisters.
They shall.
Maybe it's not a good idea to go this way.
I mean, this is where I was running away from before.
Oh, it'll work out.
I can always run back to the jungle if I have to.
Up there!
No, no!
I won't miss my mark this time.
Is he dead?
Not yet.
The man just slipped and fell into the jungle.
So you've come for me at last.
Stubborn and meddlesome, I see.
I shall be frank.
I have no intention of keeping my promise.
In other words, I refuse to go to war for you.
Still, I rather like my position as a warlord.
So, I think I shall keep it.
Also, you shall give me all the cargo on your ship quickly without complaint.
That's enough.
I won't stand for you acting like a spoiled child.
Do you honestly think we'll accept such unreasonable demands?
Haul it over, men!
Huh?
I'll do anything you want.
Order me around some more.
Put that cargo down this instant or I'll throw you overboard!
Oh, sorry.
I couldn't resist her, sir.
Porkas Deace's public execution will be exactly one week from today.
The event will be held in the town square of Marineford.
In other words, we're doing this inside of Navy Headquarters itself.
There is no doubt that Whitebeard will attempt to rescue him in the next few days.
Likely with the strength of his entire crew behind him.
Under the leadership of three admirals and with the aid of the seven warlords of the sea,
Navy Headquarters is determined to stop him at any cost.
Will you give up the title of warlord or accept your orders?
Make your decision quickly.
You've kept us waiting long enough!
I already told you I like being a warlord.
However, I loathe the world government.
I have no interest in following their orders.
Surely I can find a better solution.
Oh, I know. How does this sound?
The Marines who came to escort me had a mysterious accident.
When they were discovered, they had all been transformed into stone and were promptly disposed of.
She's planning to do something. Don't let your guard down!
I've heard about Hancock doing this before.
A merchant ship was attacked by the Kuja pirates and when it was discovered later, there weren't any crew members on board.
Just a bunch of weird statues.
Hey! Look at that! Those aren't people, are they?
You mean they were all turned to stone?
I've had enough of these threats. Your temper tantrums will not be tolerated, do you hear me?
Our big sister has a rotten personality. But in the end, she always gets her way.
Indeed. And there's a very good reason for that.
Would you like to know why? Because no matter what I do, even if I kick a kitten, even if I yank off your ears.
Why, even if I were to commit murder, the world would forgive me. And that is because, yes, it is because I am beautiful.
You're right! You can abuse me all you want, your highness!
Stop that, you fools!
The guilty thoughts swimming in your hearts shall turn your flesh to stone.
Love, love be.
Oh, I'd expect no less from a Navy Vice Admiral. Clever. Forcing the wicked thoughts from your mind with pain.
I do applaud your conviction. Though, I can't extend that compliment to your men.
They should be ashamed.
Now you're the only one left.
But one, is not zero.
Is not zero.
What?
We shall return to our peaceful home of Amazon Lily.
Aye, aye, Snake Princess!
Listen up, Boa Hancock! I won't turn away!
I refuse to return empty-handed!
Unless you reappear in two days,
your position will be revoked.
Do as you wish.
Luffy storms the Kuja village
in hopes of acquiring a boat,
but accidentally lands in a bath
where Empress Hancock is bathing.
As he peers through the steam,
rising from its waters,
sees a forbidden secret etched upon her back.
On the next, One Piece!
The secret hidden on the backs!
Luffy and the Snake Princess meet!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!